Joseph Antony

Kerala, India



josephantonykj006@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/techweed

Summary

Full stack developer with experience in developing software solutions in JavaScript for web, React Native and Android for mobile and a couple of projects in python. Knowledge is the key but the pursuit is to bring innovative ideas to life, feel free to contact.

Experience



🔇 Software Engineer

Experion Technologies

Apr 2020 - Present (6 months +)

- Developed an Anonymous Chat Room Application (Angular, Firebase)
- Developed a Global COVID19 stats application(Angular/Typescript)

🔇 Associate Software Engineer

Experion Technologies

Nov 2018 - Apr 2020 (1 year 6 months)

Worked on developing mobile application(Android/iOS) for enabling dementia patients to perform daily activities. The application was awarded a first-prize grant by the NIA (React Native/Javascript).

🔇 Software Trainee

Experion Technologies

Jul 2018 - Nov 2018 (5 months)

- Developed a Retail Management System(.Net Core, Angular, PostgreSQL).
- Worked on Utility Payment Application (Angular, Node, mongoDB, AWS).

Android Developer

Part Time & Freelancing

Feb 2017 - Jul 2018 (1 year 6 months)

- Developed an android application that could retrieve, view and share public images/videos from various social media platforms like instagram in corresponding media formats.
- Developed python script that could extract unlimited images and videos under specific tags or users which uses dynamic page scrapping.

Education

Rajagiri School of Engineering & Technology

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science 2014 - 2018

Porukara College of Education, Gagultha Monastery Campus, Champakulam East P.O, Alappuzha - 688 505

High School, Computer Science 2000 - 2014

Licenses & Certifications

- **EFSET 76 C2 Proficient** EF Standard English Test (EF SET)
- Object Oriented Python Programming Rajagiri School of Engineering & Technology
- The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google Digital Unlocked EHJ P4C G5G
- CREATE A PROFESSIONAL ONLINE PRESENCE FutureLearn

Skills

Python • AngularJS • Android • Research • Data Structures • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Mobile Applications • Digital Marketing • JavaScript • React Native